Ms. Tyler, why don't you start by telling your cousin's story?
I'm already heavy this morning. I apologize.
Don't ever apologize for that.
We'll help you. We'll carry you.
Thank you. My cousin was a loving, kind human being.
He was a girl dad, father of two daughters.
He was his mother's only son.
And I know people are probably tired of hearing me use the word amazing,
but that word actually applies to some people.
And Keith was absolutely amazing.
He brought joy wherever he went.
He was always the one to uplift his people around him,
even if you were a stranger,
and telling of who he was,
even the fact that he had only been in his apartment complex for 11 months,
and all of those people knew him, and it was a large complex.
It's a large complex, and they all knew exactly who he was
and all had good things to say about him.
And that's who he's been since he was a little boy.
You know, they really stole a Black man off of this planet
that had so much more to give,
and he had so much more to give to his daughters
and to his mother and to us as his family.
And so, on New Year's Eve,
Keith was expecting some company
and had sent his girlfriend out to get some food for the evening.
And in the interim,
you know, he heard people outside celebrating already,
and he had just got licensed for a new rifle.
And, you know,
I know people have varying opinions on shooting firearms in the air
in a celebratory manner.
But as it stands,
that's what my cousin went outside to do.
He let off a few shots.
And one of his neighbors
that happened to be an off-duty ICE agent
who was in his apartment doing who knows what,
Brian Palacios,
who we do now know for a fact is a racist,
is a child abuser,
is homophobic,
and so many other nasty things about himself,
is the person that took it upon himself
to leave his apartment,
hunt through the apartment complex
to find where he had heard the shots,
saw my cousin with his rifle,
engaged him.
He was actually in the process of returning to his home.
And this officer went back inside,
got his tactical gear,
got fully dressed in his tactical gear,
got his service pistol,
ran back through the apartment complex,
found my cousin,
and shot him dead.
After he killed my cousin,
the police response was horrendous.
They came out at least about nine cars deep,
is what the apartment complex tenants have said,
and I was privileged to receive videos as well.
They're out there in their tactical gear
while my cousin's body is laying down there in the rain.
And they're calling for Keith Porter
to surrender or shelter in place.
You cannot do both, first of all.
That's oxymoronic.
There was no medical aid rendered.
We don't even know if he was already dead
or on his last breath
and could have at least been saved.
After the fact,
they never had this officer surrender his service pistol.
They never did a sobriety check.
They never took him in for proper interrogation.
He went back into his home
and went to sleep that night.
And so from the beginning to the end,
there was no value placed on my cousin by this maniac.
And there's been no value placed on his life
by the police department,
by D.A.
Hockman,
and by the people who are in position
to actually arrest and convict this murderer.
The only reason we know who he is now
is because of current court filings and litigation,
naming him as an abuser,
as a racist,
and as the man that killed my cousin that night.
The people who have witnessed what happened
are scared for themselves
and scared for their family
because we're dealing with a fascist Trump regime.
And so here we are.
We are doing our best
to bring light to what has happened
and to get our community
and our elected officials
to pressure D.A. Hockman
to arrest this man,
to press charges,
to prosecute him
because he is nothing less than a murderer.
Thank you so much for sharing.